Finding aid to the Anne MacKay papers SSC.MS.00472
Sophia Smith Collection
- Theatre, 1943-2012; 5
  - Under Milk Wood (directed), undated (Box 10)
  - LGBT Theatre clippings, undated (Box 10)
  - Taking Liberties: Friday - Act 2, undated; 1 items (DVD ) (Box 15)
  - Taking Liberties Excerpts, 2012-02-10; 1 items (DVD) (Box 15)
  - Taking Liberties, Saturday 1984 (Lynn's Tape), 1 items (DVD) (Box 15)
  - Taking Liberties, Saturday, undated; 1 items (DVD) (Box 15)
  - Taking Liberties Cassettes, 1984; 20 items (Cassette tapes) (Box 15)
  - Midsummer Revels cassette tapes, 1982; 5 items (cassette tapes) (Box 15)
  - "Connie's opera" cassettes, undated; 2 items (cassette tapes) (Box 15)
  - "The Well of Loneliness", Southampton (cassette), 1982-08-28; 1 items (cassette tape) (Box 15)
  - Taking Liberties copy, Saturday night (VHS), 1984; 1 items (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Revels (VHS), 1982; 1 items (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Midsummer Revels (DVDs), 1982; 3 items (DVD) (Box 14)
  - Taking Liberties (DVD), 1984; 1 items (DVD) (Box 14)
  - "Taking Liberties" T-shirt, 1984 (Box 12)
  - "Revels" T-shirt, c.1982, undated (Box 12)
  - Mackay "Director of Midsummer Revels, 1982" award (Box 12)
  - Rehearsal cassette, undated; 1 items (cassette tape) (Box 15)
  - Horace Mann Theatre, undated (Box 9)
  - Horace Mann Theatre Department, undated (Box 9)
  - Horace Mann High School employment, undated (Box 9)
  - The Dalton School, 1972-1999 (Box 9)
  - Horace Mann photos and miscellaneous, 1988-1991 (Box 9)
  - Horace Mann Theatre newspaper clippings and programs, 1973-1991 (Box 9)
  - Dalton Theatre misc., 1968 (Box 9)
  - General Dalton Theatre papers, 1943-2003 (Box 9)
  - Horace Mann cassette tapes, undated; 2 items (cassette tapes) (Box 15)
- Photographs, 1910-2010; 6
  This series contains personal photographs taken by and of Mackay and her friends. Common subjects include gardens, cats, sailing, beaches, vacations, and gatherings of friends. Also included are early childhood and family photographs as well as photographs from Vassar reunions.
  - Photographs (contains originals), 1910-1990 (Box 10)
  - Photographs and newspaper clippings, 1910-1990 (Box 10)
  - Photographs, 1927-1938 (Box 10)
  - Family photographs, 1931-1939 (Box 11)
  - Photo album, 1927-1962 (Box 11)
  - Photographs, 1939-1988 (Box 11)
  - Photo album, 1977-1988 (Box 11)
  - Photo album, 1966-1976 (Box 11)
  - Slides, 1967-1969 (Box 11)
  - Photographs - sailing, 1969-1985 (Box 11)
  - Photographs and negatives, 1970-1979 (Box 11)
  - Photographs - Scotland, winter, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
  - Slides, 1973-1975 (Box 11)
  - Slides - Maine summer, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Photographs - Arsha Beach party, 1975-1978 (Box 11)
  - Slides, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Photographs - wildflowers and ICE, 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Photographs (from folder marked "Cynthia"), 1970-2000 (Box 11)
  - Photographs and negatives, 1980-1988 (Box 11)
  - Photographs (beach), 1974-1990 (Box 11)
  - Slides from Mariette Pathy Allen, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Photographs and negatives, 1991-1993 (Box 11)
  - "Wolf Girsl at Vassar" Photo, 1992-04 (Box 11)
  - Anne's house photographs, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Photo album - Scotland, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Photographs and negatives, 1994-1996 (Box 12)
  - Photos, 1997 (Box 12)
  - I.D.s and photographs, undated (Box 12)
  - Photographs and negatives, 1997-1999 (Box 12)
  - Photographs and negatives, 2000-2010 (Box 12)
  - Photo album, undated (Box 12)
  - Childhood photo album, undated (Box 12)
  - Photo album, undated (Box 12)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 12)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 12)
  - Slides, 1959-1991 (Box 13)
  - Photo Album, 1938-1954 (Box 17)
  - Cat Picture 1, undated (Box 17)
  - Cat Picture 2, undated (Box 17)
  - Birthday Card, 1973 (Folder 18)
  - Vassar graduation collage, 1949 (Folder 18)
  - Class of '49 Vassar reunion collage, 1999 (Folder 18)